(Howard:)...before my dad left
me and my mom...
(Howard:)he used to... take me
to the comic book store.
(Howard:)It was one of the few things
we did together.
(Bernadette:)Oh. Howie, I had no idea.
(Howard:)Well, I don't...
like to talk about it.
(Bernadette:)Oh, baby.
(Bernadette:)That story's made
up, isn't it?
(Howard:)That's how much buying
a comic book store means to me.
(Sheldon:)I'd like your honest
opinion on something.
(Penny:)Of course.
(Sheldon:)Now, before I start,
(Sheldon:)I need you to know that
I'm very excited about this,
(Sheldon:)and anything you say
(Sheldon:)that isn't
enthusiastically supportive
(Sheldon:)will throw our entire
relationship into question.
(Leonard:)So...
(Sheldon:)keep an open mind.
(Amy:)I'm feeling a little backed
into a corner, Sheldon.